<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<!-- 
	use to locate resources used:
	n - line number
	i - case insensitive
	I - ignore binary
	r - recursive
	grep -niIr txtToFind . 
	-->
	
    <!-- Application -->
    <string name="application_name">Gmail To Do</string>
    <string name="description_search">Search</string>
    <string name="description_save">Save</string>    
    <string name="description_sync">Sync</string>    
    <string name="description_ok">OK</string>    
    <string name="description_cancel">Cancel</string>    
    <string name="description_actions">Actions</string>   

	<!-- Settings -->
    <string name="description_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="description_general_settings">General settings</string>
	
	<!-- Account(s) -->
    <string name="description_accounts">Accounts</string>
    <string name="description_add_account">Add Google Gmail account</string>
    <string name="description_debug">Debug</string>
    <string name="description_offline_mode">Offline mode</string>
    <string name="description_accounts_authorized_to_sync">Accounts authorized to sync</string>
    <string name="description_privacy_settings">Privacy settings</string>
    <string name="description_anonymous_usage_analytics">Anonymous usage analytics</string>
	
	<!-- Task List(s) -->
    <string name="description_task_lists">Task Lists</string>
    <string name="description_task_list_create">Create Task List</string>
    <string name="description_task_list_open">Open Task List</string>
    <string name="description_task_list_rename">Rename Task List</string>
    <string name="description_task_list_delete">Delete Task List</string>
    <string name="description_task_list_clear_completed">Clear Completed</string>
    <string name="task_list_title_hint">task list title</string>
    <string name="dialog_task_list_create_message">Create a new list named</string>
    <string name="dialog_task_list_rename_message_pre">Rename list</string>
    <string name="dialog_task_list_rename_message_post">to</string>
    <string name="dialog_task_list_delete_message_pre">Do you want to delete the list</string>
    <string name="dialog_task_list_delete_message_post">The list will be permanently deleted</string>

	<!-- Task(s) -->
    <string name="description_tasks">Tasks</string>
    <string name="description_task">Task</string>
    <string name="description_task_compose">Compose Task</string>   
    <string name="description_task_edit">Edit Task</string>  
    <string name="description_task_read">Open Task</string>
    <string name="description_task_discard">Discard</string>   
    <string name="description_task_delete">Delete Task</string>

    <string name="task_title_hint">title:</string>
    <string name="task_date_hint">due date:</string>
    <string name="task_notes_hint">notes</string>
	<string name="task_unselected">Please select a task.</string>
	
	<!-- DESIGNER Account(s) -->
	
	<!-- DESIGNER Task List(s) -->
	
	<!-- DESIGNER Task(s) -->
	<string name="example_task_list_title">Example title for task list long</string>
	<string name="example_task_sort">long sort example 1</string>
	<string name="example_task_title">Example title Account takes just a few stepsasdasdasdasd.</string>
	<string name="example_task_date">Fri, Jun 26, 2011</string>
	<string name="example_task_day">Today</string>
	<string name="example_task_note">
	Example note You can use more than one Google Account on your phone (such as your home and work accounts). Adding a Google Account takes just a few steps.\n
	You can use more than one Google Account on your phone (such as your home and work accounts). Adding a Google Account takes just a few steps.\n
	You can use more than one Google Account on your phone (such as your home and work accounts). Adding a Google Account takes just a few steps.\n
	</string>

	<!-- Legal -->
	<string name="terms_of_service_part_1">
	Andorn Software Terms of Service\n
	\n
	Hello!\n
	\n
	1.\tYour relationship with Andorn Software\n
	\t1.1\tYour use of Andorn Software’s products, software, services and web sites (referred to collectively as the “Services” in this document and excluding any services provided to you by Andorn Software under a separate written agreement) is subject to the terms of a legal agreement between you and Andorn Software. “Andorn Software” means Andorn Software Incorporated, whose principal place of business is at 1466 Shallcross Ave., Orlando, FL, 32828, United States. This document explains how the agreement is made up, and sets out some of the terms of that agreement.\n
	\t1.2\tUnless otherwise agreed in writing with Andorn Software, your agreement with Andorn Software will always include, at a minimum, the terms and conditions set out in this document. These are referred to below as the “Universal Terms”.\n
	\t1.3\tYour agreement with Andorn Software will also include the terms of any Legal Notices applicable to the Services, in addition to the Universal Terms. All of these are referred to below as the “Additional Terms”. Where Additional Terms apply to a Service, these will be accessible for you to read either within, or through your use of, that Service.\n
	\t1.4\tThe Universal Terms, together with the Additional Terms, form a legally binding agreement between you and Andorn Software in relation to your use of the Services. It is important that you take the time to read them carefully. Collectively, this legal agreement is referred to below as the “Terms”.\n
	\t1.5\tIf there is any contradiction between what the Additional Terms say and what the Universal Terms say, then the Additional Terms shall take precedence in relation to that Service.\n
	\n
	2.\tAccepting the Terms\n
	\t2.1\tIn order to use the Services, you must first agree to the Terms. You may not use the Services if you do not accept the Terms.\n
	\t2.2\tYou can accept the Terms by:\n
	\t(A)\tclicking to accept or agree to the Terms, where this option is made available to you by Andorn Software in the user interface for any Service; or\n
	\t(B)\tby actually using the Services. In this case, you understand and agree that Andorn Software will treat your use of the Services as acceptance of the Terms from that point onwards.\n
	\t2.3\tYou may not use the Services and may not accept the Terms if (a) you are not of legal age to form a binding contract with Andorn Software, or (b) you are a person barred from receiving the Services under the laws of the United States or other countries including the country in which you are resident or from which you use the Services.\n
	\t2.4\tBefore you continue, you should print off or save a local copy of the Universal Terms for your records.\n
	\n
	3.\tLanguage of the Terms\n
	\t3.1\tWhere Andorn Software has provided you with a translation of the English language version of the Terms, then you agree that the translation is provided for your convenience only and that the English language versions of the Terms will govern your relationship with Andorn Software.\n
	\t3.2\tIf there is any contradiction between what the English language version of the Terms says and what a translation says, then the English language version shall take precedence.\n
	\n
	4.\tProvision of the Services by Andorn Software\n
	\t4.1\tAndorn Software is constantly innovating in order to provide the best possible experience for its users. You acknowledge and agree that the form and nature of the Services which Andorn Software provides may change from time to time without prior notice to you.\n
	\t4.2\tAs part of this continuing innovation, you acknowledge and agree that Andorn Software may stop (permanently or temporarily) providing the Services (or any features within the Services) to you or to users generally at Andorn Software’s sole discretion, without prior notice to you. You may stop using the Services at any time. You do not need to specifically inform Andorn Software when you stop using the Services.\n
	\t4.3\tYou acknowledge and agree that if Andorn Software disables access to your account, you may be prevented from accessing the Services, your account details or any files or other content which is contained in your account.\n
	\t4.4\tYou acknowledge and agree that while Andorn Software may not currently have set a fixed upper limit on the number of transmissions you may send or receive through the Services or on the amount of storage space used for the provision of any Service, such fixed upper limits may be set by Andorn Software at any time, at Andorn Software’s discretion.\n
	\n
	5.\tUse of the Services by you\n
	\t5.1\tIn order to access certain Services, you may be required to provide information about yourself (such as identification or contact details) as part of the registration process for the Service, or as part of your continued use of the Services. You agree that any registration information you give to Andorn Software will always be accurate, correct and up to date.\n
	\t5.2\tYou agree to use the Services only for purposes that are permitted by (a) the Terms and (b) any applicable law, regulation or generally accepted practices or guidelines in the relevant jurisdictions (including any laws regarding the export of data or software to and from the United States or other relevant countries).\n
	\t5.3\tYou agree not to access (or attempt to access) any of the Services by any means other than through the interface that is provided by Andorn Software, unless you have been specifically allowed to do so in a separate agreement with Andorn Software. You specifically agree not to access (or attempt to access) any of the Services through any automated means (including use of scripts or web crawlers) and shall ensure that you comply with the instructions set out in any robots.txt file present on the Services.\n
	\t5.4\tYou agree that you will not engage in any activity that interferes with or disrupts the Services (or the servers and networks which are connected to the Services).\n
	\t5.5\tUnless you have been specifically permitted to do so in a separate agreement with Andorn Software, you agree that you will not reproduce, duplicate, copy, sell, trade or resell the Services for any purpose.\n
	\t5.6 You agree that you are solely responsible for (and that Andorn Software has no responsibility to you or to any third party for) any breach of your obligations under the Terms and for the consequences (including any loss or damage which Andorn Software may suffer) of any such breach.\n
	\n
	6.\tYour passwords and account security\n
	\t6.1\tYou agree and understand that you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of passwords associated with any account you use to access the Services.\n
	\t6.2\tAccordingly, you agree that you will be solely responsible to Andorn Software for all activities that occur under your account.\n
	\t6.3\tIf you become aware of any unauthorized use of your password or of your account, you agree to notify Andorn Software immediately at chbfiv@andornsoftware.com.\n
	\n
	7.\tPrivacy and your personal information\n
	\t7.1\tThis policy explains how Andorn Software treats your personal information, and protects your privacy, when you use the Services.\n
	\t7.2 \tAndorn Software reserves the right to anonymously track and report your activity from the Services.\n
	\t7.3\tYou agree to the use of your data in accordance with Andorn Software’s privacy policies.\n
	\n
	8.\tSoftware updates\n
	\t8.1\tThe Software which you use may automatically download and install updates from time to time from Andorn Software. These updates are designed to improve, enhance and further develop the Services and may take the form of bug fixes, enhanced functions, new software modules and completely new versions. You agree to receive such updates (and permit Andorn Software to deliver these to you) as part of your use of the Services.\n
	\n
	9.\tEnding your relationship with Andorn Software\n
	\t9.1\tThe Terms will continue to apply until terminated by either you or Andorn Software as set out below.\n
	\t9.2\tIf you want to terminate your legal agreement with Andorn Software, you may do so by (a) notifying Andorn Software at any time and (b) closing your accounts for all of the Services which you use, where Andorn Software has made this option available to you. Your notice should be sent, in writing, to Andorn Software’s address which is set out at the beginning of these Terms.\n
	\t9.3\tAndorn Software may at any time, terminate its legal agreement with you if:\n
	\t(A)\tyou have breached any provision of the Terms (or have acted in manner which clearly shows that you do not intend to, or are unable to comply with the provisions of the Terms); or\n
	\t(B)\tAndorn Software is required to do so by law (for example, where the provision of the Services to you is, or becomes, unlawful); or\n
	\t(C)\tAndorn Software is transitioning to no longer providing the Services to users in the country in which you are resident or from which you use the service; or\n
	\t(D)\tthe provision of the Services to you by Andorn Software is, in Andorn Software’s opinion, no longer commercially viable.\n
	\t9.4\tNothing in this Section shall affect Andorn Software’s rights regarding provision of Services under Section 4 of the Terms.\n
	\t9.5\tWhen these Terms come to an end, all of the legal rights, obligations and liabilities that you and Andorn Software have benefited from, been subject to (or which have accrued over time whilst the Terms have been in force) or which are expressed to continue indefinitely, shall be unaffected by this cessation, and the provisions of paragraph 15.7 shall continue to apply to such rights, obligations and liabilities indefinitely.\n
	\n
	</string>
	<string name="terms_of_service_part_2">
	10.\tEXCLUSION OF WARRANTIES\n
	\t10.1\tNOTHING IN THESE TERMS, INCLUDING SECTIONS 10 AND 11, SHALL EXCLUDE OR LIMIT ANDORN SOFTWARE’S WARRANTY OR LIABILITY FOR LOSSES WHICH MAY NOT BE LAWFULLY EXCLUDED OR LIMITED BY APPLICABLE LAW. SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OF CERTAIN WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OR THE LIMITATION OR EXCLUSION OF LIABILITY FOR LOSS OR DAMAGE CAUSED BY NEGLIGENCE, BREACH OF CONTRACT OR BREACH OF IMPLIED TERMS, OR INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES. ACCORDINGLY, ONLY THE LIMITATIONS WHICH ARE LAWFUL IN YOUR JURISDICTION WILL APPLY TO YOU AND OUR LIABILITY WILL BE LIMITED TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW.\n
	\t10.2\tYOU EXPRESSLY UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT YOUR USE OF THE SERVICES IS AT YOUR SOLE RISK AND THAT THE SERVICES ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" AND “AS AVAILABLE.”\n
	\t10.3\tIN PARTICULAR, ANDORN SOFTWARE, ITS SUBSIDIARIES AND AFFILIATES, AND ITS LICENSORS DO NOT REPRESENT OR WARRANT TO YOU THAT:\n
	\t(A)\tYOUR USE OF THE SERVICES WILL MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS,\n
	\t(B)\tYOUR USE OF THE SERVICES WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED, TIMELY, SECURE OR FREE FROM ERROR,\n
	\t(C)\tANY INFORMATION OBTAINED BY YOU AS A RESULT OF YOUR USE OF THE SERVICES WILL BE ACCURATE OR RELIABLE, AND\n
	\t(D)\tTHAT DEFECTS IN THE OPERATION OR FUNCTIONALITY OF ANY SOFTWARE PROVIDED TO YOU AS PART OF THE SERVICES WILL BE CORRECTED.\n
	\t10.4\tANY MATERIAL DOWNLOADED OR OTHERWISE OBTAINED THROUGH THE USE OF THE SERVICES IS DONE AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION AND RISK AND THAT YOU WILL BE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY DAMAGE TO YOUR COMPUTER SYSTEM OR OTHER DEVICE OR LOSS OF DATA THAT RESULTS FROM THE DOWNLOAD OF ANY SUCH MATERIAL.\n
	\t10.5\tNO ADVICE OR INFORMATION, WHETHER ORAL OR WRITTEN, OBTAINED BY YOU FROM ANDORN SOFTWARE OR THROUGH OR FROM THE SERVICES SHALL CREATE ANY WARRANTY NOT EXPRESSLY STATED IN THE TERMS.\n
	\t10.6\tANDORN SOFTWARE FURTHER EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES AND CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES AND CONDITIONS OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT.\n
	\n
	11.\tLIMITATION OF LIABILITY\n
	\t11.1\tSUBJECT TO OVERALL PROVISION IN PARAGRAPH 10.1 ABOVE, YOU EXPRESSLY UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT ANDORN SOFTWARE, ITS SUBSIDIARIES AND AFFILIATES, AND ITS LICENSORS SHALL NOT BE LIABLE TO YOU FOR:\n
	\t(A)\tANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL CONSEQUENTIAL OR EXEMPLARY DAMAGES WHICH MAY BE INCURRED BY YOU, HOWEVER CAUSED AND UNDER ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY.. THIS SHALL INCLUDE, BUT NOT BE LIMITED TO, ANY LOSS OF PROFIT (WHETHER INCURRED DIRECTLY OR INDIRECTLY), ANY LOSS OF GOODWILL OR BUSINESS REPUTATION, ANY LOSS OF DATA SUFFERED, COST OF PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES, OR OTHER INTANGIBLE LOSS;\n
	\t(B)\tANY LOSS OR DAMAGE WHICH MAY BE INCURRED BY YOU, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO LOSS OR DAMAGE AS A RESULT OF:\n
	\t(I)\tANY RELIANCE PLACED BY YOU ON THE COMPLETENESS, ACCURACY OR EXISTENCE OF ANY ADVERTISING, OR AS A RESULT OF ANY RELATIONSHIP OR TRANSACTION BETWEEN YOU AND ANY ADVERTISER OR SPONSOR WHOSE ADVERTISING APPEARS ON THE SERVICES;\n
	\t(II)\tANY CHANGES WHICH ANDORN SOFTWARE MAY MAKE TO THE SERVICES, OR FOR ANY PERMANENT OR TEMPORARY CESSATION IN THE PROVISION OF THE SERVICES (OR ANY FEATURES WITHIN THE SERVICES);\n
	\t(III) THE DELETION OF, CORRUPTION OF, OR FAILURE TO STORE, ANY CONTENT AND OTHER COMMUNICATIONS DATA MAINTAINED OR TRANSMITTED BY OR THROUGH YOUR USE OF THE SERVICES;\n
	\t(III)\tYOUR FAILURE TO PROVIDE ANDORN SOFTWARE WITH ACCURATE ACCOUNT INFORMATION;\n
	\t(IV)\tYOUR FAILURE TO KEEP YOUR PASSWORD OR ACCOUNT DETAILS SECURE AND CONFIDENTIAL;\n
	\t11.2\tTHE LIMITATIONS ON ANDORN SOFTWARE’S LIABILITY TO YOU IN PARAGRAPH 15.1 ABOVE SHALL APPLY WHETHER OR NOT ANDORN SOFTWARE HAS BEEN ADVISED OF OR SHOULD HAVE BEEN AWARE OF THE POSSIBILITY OF ANY SUCH LOSSES ARISING.\n
	\n
	12.\tAdvertisements\n
	\t12.1\tSome of the Services are supported by advertising revenue and may display advertisements and promotions. These advertisements may be targeted to the content of information stored on the Services, queries made through the Services or other information.\n
	\t12.2\tThe manner, mode and extent of advertising by Andorn Software on the Services are subject to change without specific notice to you.\n
	\t12.3\tIn consideration for Andorn Software granting you access to and use of the Services, you agree that Andorn Software may place such advertising on the Services.\n
	\n
	13.\tOther content\n
	\t13.1\tThe Services may include hyperlinks to other web sites or content or resources. Andorn Software may have no control over any web sites or resources which are provided by companies or persons other than Andorn Software.\n
	\t13.2\tYou acknowledge and agree that Andorn Software is not responsible for the availability of any such external sites or resources, and does not endorse any advertising, products or other materials on or available from such web sites or resources.\n
	\t13.3\tYou acknowledge and agree that Andorn Software is not liable for any loss or damage which may be incurred by you as a result of the availability of those external sites or resources, or as a result of any reliance placed by you on the completeness, accuracy or existence of any advertising, products or other materials on, or available from, such web sites or resources.\n
	\n
	14.\tChanges to the Terms\n
	\t14.1\tAndorn Software may make changes to the Universal Terms or Additional Terms from time to time. When these changes are made, Andorn Software will make a new copy of the Universal Terms available and any new Additional Terms will be made available to you from within, or through, the affected Services.\n
	\t14.2\tYou understand and agree that if you use the Services after the date on which the Universal Terms or Additional Terms have changed, Andorn Software will treat your use as acceptance of the updated Universal Terms or Additional Terms.\n
	\n
	15. General legal terms\n
	\t15.1\tSometimes when you use the Services, you may (as a result of, or through your use of the Services) use a service or download a piece of software, or purchase goods, which are provided by another person or company. Your use of these other services, software or goods may be subject to separate terms between you and the company or person concerned. If so, the Terms do not affect your legal relationship with these other companies or individuals.\n
	\t15.2\tThe Terms constitute the whole legal agreement between you and Andorn Software and govern your use of the Services (but excluding any services which Andorn Software may provide to you under a separate written agreement), and completely replace any prior agreements between you and Andorn Software in relation to the Services.\n
	\t15.3\tYou agree that Andorn Software may provide you with notices, including those regarding changes to the Terms, by email, regular mail, or postings on the Services.\n
	\t15.4\tYou agree that if Andorn Software does not exercise or enforce any legal right or remedy which is contained in the Terms (or which Andorn Software has the benefit of under any applicable law), this will not be taken to be a formal waiver of Andorn Software’s rights and that those rights or remedies will still be available to Andorn Software.\n
	\t15.5\tIf any court of law, having the jurisdiction to decide on this matter, rules that any provision of these Terms is invalid, then that provision will be removed from the Terms without affecting the rest of the Terms. The remaining provisions of the Terms will continue to be valid and enforceable.\n
	\t15.7\tYou agree that Andorn Software shall still be allowed to apply for injunctive remedies (or an equivalent type of urgent legal relief) in any jurisdiction.\n
	\n
	September 30, 2011\n
	</string>
</resources>
